<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Django Jobs Unified Feed</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/</link><description>Unified deduplicated Django jobs feed</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Infrastructure Engineer, Python Software Foundation</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/8044/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">infrastructure engineer|python software foundation</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:04:33 +0000</pubDate><description>Job Title Infrastructure Engineer Job Description The Python Software Foundation (PSF) is hiring a full-time Infrastructure Engineer, reporting to the PSF&#x27;s Director of Engineering. The mission of the Python Software Foundation is to promote, protect, and advance the Python programming language, and to support and facilitate the growth of a diverse and international community of Python programmers. In support of our mission, the PSF manages the infrastructure that provides resources and download</description><company>Python Software Foundation</company><location>Remote, USA</location><salary>$95K - 125K</salary><company_url>https://jobs.pyfound.org</company_url><apply_url></apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://jobs.pyfound.org&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Senior Python Backend Developer, SKYCATCHFIRE</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/8030/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">senior python backend developer|skycatchfire</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:17:44 +0000</pubDate><description>Job Title Senior Python Backend Developer Job Description Transform spreadsheet-driven complexity into clean, scalable backend systems. This role focuses on designing robust Python backends that turn complex business processes into elegant data models and reliable APIs. You will work as a backend architect, deeply understanding how businesses operate and building systems that scale effortlessly. The work prioritizes long-term reliability, clarity, and high-quality execution over quick fixes. Vis</description><company>SKYCATCHFIRE</company><location>Canton, OH, USA</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://www.skycatchfire.com</company_url><apply_url></apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://www.skycatchfire.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Senior Python Developer, Cial Dun &amp; Bradstreet</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/8019/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">senior python developer|cial dun bradstreet</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:40:10 +0000</pubDate><description>Job Title Senior Python Developer Job Description As a Senior Python Developer at CIAL Dun &amp; Bradstreet, your primary responsibility is to design, develop, and maintain scalable backend services and performant web applications using frameworks such as Django, Flask, or FastAPI. You will play a central role in the data lifecycle by building robust ETL processes and sophisticated web scrapers to transform raw information into actionable business insights. ​On the technical side, you will manage co</description><company>Cial Dun &amp; Bradstreet</company><location>São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://cialdnb.bamboohr.com</company_url><apply_url></apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://cialdnb.bamboohr.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Founding Full-Stack Senior Engineer (UK ONLY) - Fully Remote, MyDataValue</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/8014/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">founding full stack senior engineer uk only fully remote|mydatavalue</guid><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:44:45 +0000</pubDate><description>Job Title Founding Full-Stack Senior Engineer (UK ONLY) - Fully Remote Job Description £70k – £90k • 0.5% – 2.0% • Fully Remote We are an AI-driven Hospitality Tech platform helping vacation rental owners automate their revenue on Booking.com. Unlike most &quot;early-stage&quot; startups, we are already at £100k ARR, growing month-on-month and have investment from angels. We have a product customers love, a validated business model, and we are now preparing to expand to Airbnb and Expedia. We are a lean t</description><company>MyDataValue</company><location>London, ---, United Kingdom</location><salary>70k</salary><company_url>https://www.mydatavalue.com</company_url><apply_url></apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://www.mydatavalue.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Python / Django Developer, Client of Foxley Talent</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/8010/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">python django developer|client of foxley talent</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:37:13 +0000</pubDate><description>Job Title Python / Django Developer Job Description Build and maintain web applications using Python and the Django framework Design and implement backend logic, database models, and user profile systems for community and contributor focused functionality Implement mailing list and newsletter systems that help users stay connected with community activity Collaborate with an external partners Build systems that recognise contributors through profile features, participation tracking, through GitHu</description><company>Client of Foxley Talent</company><location>Remote, United States</location><salary>$120,000</salary><company_url>https://foxleytalent.com</company_url><apply_url></apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://foxleytalent.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Staff Software Engineer, Bluebird Kids Health</title><link>https://www.python.org/jobs/8009/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">staff software engineer|bluebird kids health</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:38:52 +0000</pubDate><description>Job Title Staff Software Engineer Job Description We’re hiring a Staff Software Engineer to play a foundational role on our engineering team. You’ll be joining a newly formed team of three engineers, collaborating on technical direction and fostering shared growth as we build the operating system for pediatric care. In this role, you’ll architect and build robust backend systems, scalable data workflows, and intuitive interfaces for families and care teams. You’ll partner closely with clinical o</description><company>Bluebird Kids Health</company><location>Boston, MA, United States of America</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://www.linkedin.com</company_url><apply_url></apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://www.linkedin.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Software Engineer @ RINSE</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2310/software-engineer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">software engineer|rinse</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Rinse provides dry cleaning and laundry delivery services to customers in twelve metropolitan areas in the US and Canada. The engineering team is distributed across the United States and internationally and has been entirely remote for years, though a desk can be provided in listed cities. Open to newly-graduated and more senior engineers who meet the bar. Looking for true full-stack engineers with strong React / Typescript / CSS skills and comfort in a Python / Django environment. Also seeking </description><company>RINSE</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/eaf43cde-bdf4-4873-858d-fc6f27da6a65</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Staff Engineer @ Blueberry Pediatrics</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2300/staff-engineer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">staff engineer|blueberry pediatrics</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Blueberry Pediatrics provides affordable, high-quality pediatric telemedicine with board-certified pediatricians and at-home medical kits, available 24/7. The company is growing its B2B and D2C business and seeks senior/full-stack engineering talent to help deliver this product. The role emphasizes engineering ingenuity, alignment with patient-first outcomes, and collaboration with a product team. Technologies mentioned include Django, Hotwire Turbo (HTMX-like), PyTorch, scikit-learn, and Flutte</description><company>Blueberry Pediatrics</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/09c6b1e1-4482-4657-96dd-5a5363b9cafc</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Founding Engineer @ myDataValue.com</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2302/founding-engineer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">founding engineer|mydatavalue com</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>We are an AI-driven Hospitality Tech platform helping vacation rental owners automate their revenue on Booking.com. We are bootstrapped, profitable (£100k ARR), and growing month-on-month. We are looking for a Founding Engineer (Python/Django) to partner with us (2 founders) and scale our infrastructure. This is a fullstack role (React) involving high-volume scraping, browser automation &amp; agents. Stack: Python, Django, Postgres, React. Challenge: Enterprise-scale scraping (1000s req/s), reverse </description><company>myDataValue.com</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/e44cb301-e062-4773-81f7-a4d9fde42dfe</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Senior Django Developer @ SKYCATCHFIRE</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2303/senior-django-developer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">senior django developer|skycatchfire</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Our team transforms complex business operations into elegant, reliable systems. We prioritize &quot;Email &gt; Meetings&quot; and protected focus time to ensure we build robust Django backends properly rather than settling for quick fixes. If you’re a self-motivated pro who takes pride in mastering your craft and using AI to work smarter, we offer a stable, predictable environment to solve deep technical challenges. For full info, visit: https://www.skycatchfire.com/careers/django-developer/ Open roles: http</description><company>SKYCATCHFIRE</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/d6d7883f-89e0-4ffe-9664-9a66b4adea38</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Founding Engineer @ Halfpricesoft</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2307/founding-engineer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">founding engineer|halfpricesoft</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Halfpricesoft, a profitable bootstrapped company in the small business payroll and tax compliance space, is transitioning legacy solutions to a modern cloud-native suite and seeks a Founding Engineer. You will report directly to the Founder, own the technical roadmap, help build and mentor the engineering team, lead the transition from legacy systems to modern cloud architecture, and manage/scale Kubernetes deployments. Tech stack includes Python (Django), React, Kubernetes, and other cloud-nati</description><company>Halfpricesoft</company><location>Berkeley, CA</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/56a54360-2ee4-4d1c-af71-39b8346ded71</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Founding Engineer (Full-Stack) @ DrSwarm</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2309/founding-engineer-full-stack</link><guid isPermaLink="false">founding engineer full stack|drswarm</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>DrSwarm is building AI-driven workflow automation for healthcare clinics / health systems (scheduling, RCM/billing workflows, patient ops). This is a true 0→1 role: ship fast, talk to customers, own systems end-to-end. You will: - Build product end-to-end (Next.js + Django) - Ship integrations + workflow automation (APIs, webhooks, background jobs, queues) - Own reliability (logs/metrics, retries, failure modes) and pragmatic security (HIPAA-aware) Stack: Next.js, React/TypeScript, Django/Python</description><company>DrSwarm</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/a5d7f5be-6cc8-4c23-b3ce-6c9ac12d45e9</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Senior Backend Developer @ thelab</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2311/senior-backend-developer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">senior backend developer|thelab</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>We&#x27;re a digital agency focused on e-commerce, marketing, creative production and increasingly, AI-powered workflows to make our own teams more productive. We&#x27;re hiring a senior backend developer to lead a greenfield ML/NLP project building workflow automations across image production, design, analytics/performance reporting and more. You&#x27;ll work on a growing team on the technical side with access to talent in every department as we build tools to support our internal processes.</description><company>thelab</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/be027e38-8c42-4432-be6f-b1b339b6b028</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item><item><title>Senior Backend Engineer (AI Systems) @ Waypoint AI</title><link>https://builtwithdjango.com/jobs/2312/senior-backend-engineer-ai-systems</link><guid isPermaLink="false">senior backend engineer ai systems|waypoint ai</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 05:46:22 +0000</pubDate><description>Waypoint AI is a Czech-American B2B startup building &quot;Chip&quot;, an AI support engineer that autonomously triages, routes, and resolves complex technical support cases. Raised $3.1M and already in production with customers including Volvo and ClickHouse. Small engineering team; using AI (e.g., Claude) as a collaborator. Hiring for Senior Backend Engineer (AI Systems), Fullstack Engineer, and Frontend Developer. Office in Prague 7 (Holešovice), remote-friendly. To apply, email joinus@mywaypoint.ai wi</description><company>Waypoint AI</company><location>Remote</location><salary></salary><company_url>https://gettjalerts.com</company_url><apply_url>https://gettjalerts.com/jobs/c5e6a28e-8a58-4818-abe3-891299e8171d</apply_url><image_url>https://t0.gstatic.com/faviconV2?client=SOCIAL&amp;type=FAVICON&amp;fallback_opts=TYPE,SIZE,URL&amp;url=https://gettjalerts.com&amp;size=128</image_url></item></channel></rss>
